ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- GP Cotton Dust CDS - CBLA - Participants in Lawsuit Management, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 27)
- GP Cotton Dust CBLA Testimony, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 28)
- GP Cotton Dust Company Statements re Cost Savings, 1975-1976 (Box 100, Folder 29)
- Cotton Dust Commerce Department, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 30)
- GP Cotton Dust Congress, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 31)
- GP Cotton Dust Consultants, 1976-1977 (Box 100, Folder 32)
- GP Cotton Dust Cotton, Inc., 1978-1979 (Box 100, Folder 33)
- GP Cotton Dust COWPS, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 34)
- GP General Media Clips, 1978-1979 (Box 100, Folder 35)
- GP Cotton Dust CDS, 1972-1978 (Box 100, Folder 36)
- GP Cotton Dust Delay - Legal Documents, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 37)
- GP Cotton Dust Standard Discharges (breathing test), 1981 (Box 100, Folder 38)
- GP Cotton Dust, Dust Control - Clippings, 1971-1978 (Box 100, Folder 39)
- GP Cotton Dust Economic Impact, 1980 (Box 100, Folder 40)
- GP Cotton Dust CDS -- Economic Advantages Interference I-Doc., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 41)
- GP Cotton Dust CDS - Economic Advantage Interference II - Notes, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 1)
- GP Cotton Dust Economic Advantage Interference III Clippings, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 2)
- GP Cotton Dust Worksheets I Economic Feasibility, 1975-1978 (Box 101, Folder 3)
- GP Cotton Dust Environmental Impact Statement, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 4)
- GP Cotton Dust Health Effects - MISC, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 5)
- GP Cotton Dust Implementation I Conference, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 6)
- GP Cotton Dust Implementation III Burlington-Erwin Mills, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 7)
- GP General Cotton Dust Standard Implementation IV Ed. Materials, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 8)
- GP General Cotton Dust Standard Implementation V - OSHA Directive, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 9)
- GP General Cotton Dust Standard Implementation VI ACTWU, 1980 (Box 101, Folder 10)
- GP Cotton Dust Johnston Amendment, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 11)
- GP Cotton Dust Kincaid, Correspondence., etc., 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 12)
- Labor Department Memo, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 13)
- GP Cotton Dust Leaflet, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 14)
- GP Cotton Dust Merchant (Other than NIOSH), 1978-1981 (Box 101, Folder 15)
- Cotton Dust Media Project, 1978-1981 (Box 101, Folder 16)
- GP Cotton Dust Mandatory Removal, 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 17)
- GP Cotton Dust Machinery Manufacturing Company Data, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 18)
- GP Cotton Dust Misc - CDS - Worksheets III, 1976-1978 (Box 101, Folder 19)
- GP Cotton Dust NIOSH I (Government Testimony), 1973-1978 (Box 101, Folder 20)
- GP Cotton Dust NIOSH II Misc, 1973-1977 (Box 101, Folder 21)
- OSHA Enforcement Manual Cotton Dust Standard, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 22)
- GP Cotton Dust Post-Hearing (ACTWU), 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 23)
- GP Cotton Dust Hearing - Procedural Matters, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 24)
- GP Cotton Dust Publicity Pamphlet, 1970-1981 (Box 101, Folder 25)
- GP Cotton Dust Research and Development: Office of Science and Technology - U.S. Department of Communication, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 26)
- GP Cotton Dust Racial Diff's: Lung Function, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 27)
- GP Cotton Dust Reist, Parker, 1976-1977 (Box 101, Folder 28)
- GP Cotton Dust Sampling Method, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 29)
- GP Cotton Dust Senate Labor Subcommittee Hearing, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 30)
- GP Cotton Dust Stevens, (J. P.), 1978 (Box 101, Folder 31)
- GP Cotton Dust Synthetics, Shift To, 1976-1977 (Box 101, Folder 32)
- GP Cotton Dust Seminario, Correspondence., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 33)
- Cotton Dust Standard Supreme Court, 1979-1981 (Box 101, Folder 34)
- GP Cotton Dust Worksheet II Technological Feasibility, 1974-1977 (Box 101, Folder 35)
- GP Cotton Dust Text, Summaries, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 36)
- Cotton Dust Standard USDA, 1978-1982 (Box 101, Folder 37)
- USDOL Stand, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 38)
- Cotton Dust Standard Washed Cotton, 1981 (Box 101, Folder 39)
- GP Cotton Dust Waste Processing, 1978-1979 (Box 101, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Airguard Industries Louisville, Kentucky, 1978-1989 (Box 102, Folder 1)
- Allesons' of Rochester Geneva, New York, 1984-1988 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Allied Leather, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Allied Split Johnstown, New York, 1988-1990 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Alton Box Mobile, Alabama (Box 102, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Arrow Company Jasper, Alabama, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Asher Slacks Fitchburg, Massachusetts, 1994 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Aspen Ribbon Company Lafayette, Colorado, 1987-1990 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Arrow Company (subs. West-Point Pepperell, Inc.) Bremen, Georgia, 1987-1989 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Arrow Shirt Company, (subs. Cluett Peabody Company) Elysburg, Pennsylvania, 1980-1991 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Anniston Sportswear, Inc. (Div. Jaymar-Ruby, Inc.), 1988 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- OSH Case bates Nitewear (Gerber Products) North Carolina, 1988-1989 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- OSH Case BASF - Inc. General, 1978-1988 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Best Cleaners, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Big Yank Corporation Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 1988-1993 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Sam Bonk Uniform and Civilian Cap Company, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Bradford Dyeing Association, Inc. Westerly, Rhode Island, 1983-1988 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Bondo Atlanta, Georgia, 1994-1995 (Box 102, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Brockway Plastics, Inc. Belvidere, New Jersey, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Bronxwood Dyeing Company, Inc. Bronx, New York, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Brown Group, Inc., 21 (Box 102, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Fredericktown, Missouri, 1991 (Box 102, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Company Cape Girardeau, Missouri, 1989-1990 (Box 102, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Company, 1986-1990 (Box 102, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Company St. Louis, Missouri Collective Bargaining, 1988-1990 (Box 102, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Company Piedmont, MO, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Brown Shoe Company Pocahontas, Arizona, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Cameo Curtain, Inc. New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Cadillac Industry, Inc. Mayaguez, Puerto Rico, 1988 (Box 102, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Cavalier Clothes Jamaica, New York, 1993 (Box 102, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Celion Carbon Fibers, 1990 (Box 102, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Chris Craft Industrial Products Inc. Waterford, New York, 1988-1995 (Box 102, Folder 32)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973-1988 (Box 102, Folder 33)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 34)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Chemical), 1976-1979 (Box 102, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Columbus Coated Fabric/Borden Inc. OSHRC Docket #88-2893, 1989 (Box 102, Folder 36)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 37)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 11 Company, 1976-1977 (Box 102, Folder 38)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 1 ACTWU, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 39)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 111 Other, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 40)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics #1V - Lewis' Records, 1974-1977 (Box 102, Folder 41)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number V NIOSH, 1973-1976 (Box 102, Folder 42)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Environmental Monitoring, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 43)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Box 102, Folder 44)
- OSH Case Columbus Coated Fabric/Borden, 1989 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabric (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 11 Company, 1976-1977 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 1 ACTWU, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 111, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number 1V-Lewis' Records, 1974-1977 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Number V - NIOSH, 1973-1976 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics Environmental Monitoring, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- OSHA Case State Materials Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case Clippings Columbus Coated Fabrics, (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1972-1977 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Commercial Filters Tall City, IN, 1975-1989 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Congress Textile Printers, Paterson, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Cone Mills Corporation General Cotton Dust, 1980-1983 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Cone Mills Edna Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Cone Mills Salisbury Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Cone Mills Tabardrey Plant, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Connellsville Sportswear Connellsville, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- OSHA Case Craddock-Terry Corporation, Blackstone, Virginia, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- OSHA Case Craftex Mills, Inc. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1971-1975 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Crown Yarn Dye Company Inc. South Attleboro, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- OSHA Case Cryogenic Structures, Inc. Central Valley, New York, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Crystal Zoo, Boulder, Colorado, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Damon Creations Damon International, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Dan River Mills, Danville, Virginia, 1985 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Dartmouth Woolen Mills, Inc. Claremont, New Hampshire, 1978-1984 (Box 103, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Decker Corporation Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 103, Folder 26)
- De Poortere Corporation, Wilmington, Delaware, 1981-1983 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Donaldson Company, Inc. Isanti, Minnesota, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Downs Carpet Company, Willow Grove, Pennsylvania, 1987-1991 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Duluth Community Action Program, Duluth, Minnesota, 1983-1985 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Duo Temp Div. of Crestline Corporation, Depew, New York, 1983-1993 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- OSH Case E and W Piece Dye Workers, Inc. Harristown, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Eagle Knitting Mills Shawano, Wisconsin, 1984 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Eagle Shirtmakers Inc. subs. Crystal Brands, Inc. Mahoney City, Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Eastern Piece Dye Works Long Island City, New York, 1983 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Echlin, Inc. General, 1985-1989 (Box 103, Folder 36)
- Echlin, Inc. Friction Materials Company Division Lawrence, Massachusetts, 1987-1990 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Eddington Thread, Eddington, Pennsylvania, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- OSHA Case Efka Plastic Corporation Bayonne, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Elk Piece Dye Works, Inc. Garnerville, New York, 1983-1990 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Elk Piece Dye Works Peter Ruzzi, 1984-1990 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Emerson Textile (Chelsea Industries, Inc.) Chelsea, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Elite Silk Screen Engraving Company, Hawthorne, New Jersey (Box 104, Folder 7)
- OSH Case F. Englert Dyeing Company, West New York, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- OSH Case The Enro Shirt Company, Louisville, Kentucky, 1987-1991 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Everlon Fabrics, Inc. subs. Nabisco, Inc. Cape May, New Jersey, 1981 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Everlon Fabrics Corporation Camp May County Ind. Park Rio Grande, New Jersey, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Exide Corporation Cheektowaga, New York, 1978-1985 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Facemate Corporation, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Fasco Coated Products, Orangeburg, New York, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Feuer Leather Corporation, Johnstown, New York, 1986-1989 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- OSHA Case Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. Eden, North Carolina, 1977-1986 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. Eden, North Carolina, 1982-1993 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- OSHA Case Fieldcrest Mills, Eden, North Carolina, 1978-1986 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Mills Collective Bargaining, 1984-1987 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- OSHA Case Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. (Karastan Rug Mill) Eden, North Carolina, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Fieldcrest Mills, Inc. Cotton Dust Contract Revisions, 1979-1982 (Box 104, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Fiber Dynamics Highpoint, Highpoint, North Carolina, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- OSHA Case Fiberglass of Canada Guelph, Ontario, 1978 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Fiberglass Hazards Presglass, Inc. Greenfield, IN, 1987 (Box 104, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Fun-Shu, Ltd. West Hazelton, Pennsylvania, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- OSHA Case Futura Fabrics Corporation Hazelton, Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Flushing Shirt Company, Frostburg, Maryland, 1989 (Box 104, Folder 27)
- OSHA Case FMC Corporation General, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 28)
- OSHA Case FMC Corporation Fredericksburg, Virginia, 1977 (Box 104, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Finley Industries, Finley, Ohio, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Fishman and Tobin, 1985-1989 (Box 104, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Fleisher Finishing, Inc. Waterbury, Connecticut, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Flock Fibers, Inc. Concord, New Hampshire, 1982 (Box 104, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Flock Industries, Phillipsburg, New Jersey, 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Gale-Sobel Company, St. Louis, Missouri, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 35)
- OSHA Case Garden State Tannery, Inc. (subs. Walter Kidde and Company, Inc.) Fleetwood, Pennsylvania (Leather Industry), 1977-1987 (Box 104, Folder 36)
- OSH Case Genesco Inc. Hagaman, New York, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 37)
- OSH Case Glenmore Plastics Ind. Brooklyn, New York, 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 38)
- OSH Case Goldtex, Goldsboro, North Carolina, 1981-1990 (Box 104, Folder 39)
- OSHA Case Gordonsville Industries, Inc. Gordonsville, Virginia, 1977-1987 (Box 104, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Graber Company, Saginaw, Michigan, 1979-1982 (Box 104, Folder 41)
- OSH Case W. R. Grace and Company Adams, Massachusetts, 1980-1986 (Box 104, Folder 42)
- OSH Case Graniteville Company, Augusta, Georgia, 1980-1981 (Box 104, Folder 43)
- OSH Case Green Lane Hosiery Company, Inc. Green Lane, Pennsylvania, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 44)
- L. Greif and Company (Middleburg Manufacturing Division) Hanover, Pennsylvania, 1978-1982 (Box 104, Folder 45)
- OSH Case Guild Dyers, Inc. West New York, New Jersey (Box 104, Folder 46)
- OSH Case Gulf Apparel Company, Macon, Georgia, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 47)
- OSHA Case Gurney Industries, Inc. (Gurney Manufacturing Division) Prattville, Alabama Folder Number 1, 1979-1983 (Box 104, Folder 48)
- OSHA Case Gurney Industries, Inc. (Gurney Manufacturing Division) Prattville, Alabama Folder Number 3, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 49)
- OSH Case GWG Jeans Winnipeg, Manitoba, Canada, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 50)
- OSH Case Hagaman Finishing, Gloversville, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Hardis Brothers Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1986 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Hartmarx - Kuppenheimer Div. Loganville, Georgia, 1990-1993 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- OSH Case C. F. Hathaway Company, Dover-Foxcraft, Me., 1981-1988 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- OSHA Case Hayward-Schuster Woolen Mills, East Douglas, Massachusetts, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Health-Tex, Inc. Cumberland, Rhode Island, 1979-1986 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Health-Tex, Inc. Central Falls, Rhode Island, 1987-1988 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Health Tex Gadsden, Alabama, 1984 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Health-Tex, Inc. Gardiner, ME, 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case Health-Tex, Inc. Guin, Alabama, 1977-1984 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Health-Tex Company, Brusnwick, ME, 1979-1986 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Health-Tex Company, Portland, Maine, 1979-1984 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Health-Tex, Inc. (Diamond Hill) Providence, Rhode Island, 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- OSH Case - Highland Yarn Mills - Clipping High Point, North Carolina, 1991-1994 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Highland Yarn Mills Docket Number 92-3245, 1992-1993 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Highland Yarn Company, High Point, North Carolina, 1980-1990 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Hooker Chemical Hicksville, New York, 1980-1981 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- OSH Case IPC Limited Partnership Bristol, New Hampshire, 1982-1990 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- OSHA Case IRC Fibers Painesville, Ohio, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Ithaca Industries Inc. Swainsboro, Georgia, 1988 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- OSHA Case Hull Dye and Print Works, Inc. Derby, Connecticut, 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Imco Containers, Inc. Lewistown, Pennsylvania, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Training Imco Container Corporation Belvidere, New Jersey, 1981 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Industrial Knitted Fabrics and Finishing Corporation Amsterdam, New York, 1980-1983 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- OSHA Case Inman Fiber Inc. Charlotte, North Carolina, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Independence Plating Company Paterson, New Jersey (Box 105, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Inmont Company Toledo, Ohio, 1979 (Box 105, Folder 27)
- OSH Case International Packings Northfield, New Hampshire, 1980-1984 (Box 105, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Jacques, A. Dyers, Inc. New York, New York, 1983 (Box 105, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Janesville Products Norwalk, Ohio, 1980-1984 (Box 105, Folder 30)
- OSH Case Jaymar-Ruby Company Rector, Arizona, 1990 (Box 105, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Jefferson Smurfit Corporation Mount Home, North Carolina, 1986-1988 (Box 105, Folder 32)
- OSHA Case Johnson and Johnson (ESDP) New Brunswick, New Jersey, 1975-1984 (Box 106, Folder 1)
- OSHA Case Johnson and Johnson (Ethicon, Inc.) Somerville, New Jersey, 1974-1986 (Box 106, Folder 2)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson ETO Issues, 1982-1986 (Box 106, Folder 3)
- OSHA Case Johnson and Johnson General - ETO Hazard, 1981-1982 (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Johnstown Leather Corporation, Johnstown, New York, 1982-1989 (Box 106, Folder 5)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson Advisory Council, 1984-1985 (Box 106, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Juvenile Shoes, 1989 (Box 106, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson South Africa, 1986 (Box 106, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson Drug Testing, 1987-1997 (Box 106, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Johnson and Johnson OSH Research, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Kendall Company Walpole, Massachusetts, 1971-1983 (Box 106, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Keuffel and Esser Company Taconic, New York, 1976-1981 (Box 106, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Kleen Brite Labs. Inc. Brockport, New York 100 Fair Street, 1988-1990 (Box 106, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Kleenbrite Labs. Inc. Brockport, New York State Street, 1988-1990 (Box 106, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Leader Dyeing and Finishing Company, Inc. Paterson, New Jersey, 1988-1989 (Box 106, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Lebaron-Louis Roth Los Angeles, California, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- OSH Case Louisiana Plastics, Inc. Division of Bemis Corporation, Louisiana, MO, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- OSH Case M. Lowenstein Morganton, North Carolina, Doplin Plant, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- OSH Case Ludlow Textiles, Indianola, Mississippi, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- OSH Case Ludlow Textiles, Ludlow, Maryland, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- OSHA Case Magee Carpet Company Bloomsburg, Pennsylvania, 1979-1988 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- OSH Case Malden Mills, Inc. Barre, Vermont, 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- OSH Case Manchester Die Company Inc. Manchester, New Hampshire, 1982-1988 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- OSH Case Manhattan Shirt Company, Americus, Georgia, 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- OSHA Case Maue Weaving Corporation N. Y. C. (and Elysburg, Pennsylvania), 1977 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Medalist/Sandknit Company Wanpun, Wisconsin, 1984 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Medi-Clean (Angelica Corporation) Rome, Georgia, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- Puerto Rico Joint Board re: Cadillac Industries, 1988 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- OSH Case Sam Miller Bag Company, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Mobile Corporation Paulsboro, New Jersey (Box 107, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Monmouth Plastics Inc. Asbury Park, New Jersey, 1981-1986 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- OSHA Case Monroe Print Works, Inc. Monroe, North Carolina, 1979-1987 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- OSHA Case Mount Vernon Mills, West Columbia, South Carolina, 1978-1979 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Munsingwear, Inc. Ashland, Wisconsin, 1982-1987 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Musingwear, Inc. Hamilton, Alabama, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- OSHA Case Munsingwear, Inc. Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1978-1981 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- Myrna Shoe, Manchester, New Hampshire, 1984-1985 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Native Textiles Glens Falls, New York, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- OSHA Case Nicolet Industries, Inc. Norristown, Pennsylvania, 1976-1980 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Niki-Lu Ind. Talladega, Alabama, 1982 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Northern Feather Company, Newark, New Jersey, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- OSH Case OK Towel Co. Elizabeth, New Jersey, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Orbit Industries, Bronx, New York, 1983-1985 (Box 107, Folder 28)
- OSH Case Pacific-Columbia Mills, M. Lowenstein and Sons, Inc. Columbia, South Carolina - Olympia Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 107, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Pellon Corp. Hopkinsville, Kentucky, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 30)
- OSHA Case Pendleton Woolen Mills Washougal, Washington, 1978-1983 (Box 107, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Pickett Cotton Mills, High Point, North Carolina, 1981-1983 (Box 107, Folder 32)
- OSH Case Pike Manufacturing, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Pioneer Parachute, Manchester, Connecticut, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Plano Metal Specialties Inc. (Box 107, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Plummer Precision Optica, Pennsburg, Pennsylvania, 1989 (Box 107, Folder 36)
- OSH Case PM Fabric Printing, Inc. New York, New York (Box 107, Folder 37)
- OSH Case Porritt and Spencer, Inc. Wilson, North Carolina, 1987 (Box 107, Folder 38)
- Case Prestolite/Allied Chemical, Sanford, Maine, 1980 (Box 107, Folder 39)
- OSHA Case Printex Corp. Ossining, New York, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Putnam-Herzl Finishing, Company, Inc. Putnam, Connecticut, 1983-1985 (Box 107, Folder 41)
- OSH Case R. C. Tex. PTG. Brooklyn, New York, 1985 (Box 107, Folder 42)
- OSH Case Rendell Paper Co. Rochester, New York, 1987-1988 (Box 107, Folder 43)
- OSH Case Rexham Corp. Edinburgh, Ind., 1978-1982 (Box 107, Folder 44)
- OSH Case Rock Castle Mfg. Mount Vernon, Kentucky, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 45)
- OSH Case Rosen Textile Engraving, Agawam, Massachusetts, 1983 (Box 107, Folder 46)
- OSH Case Petcar Textile Dyers and Finishers, Brooklyn, New York, 1981-1983 (Box 107, Folder 47)
- OSH Case Phoenix Dye, Brunswick, Ohio, 1979 (Box 107, Folder 48)
- OSHA Case Rock Hill Printing and Finishing Co. Rock Hill, South Carolina, 1977-1985 (Box 107, Folder 49)
- OSH Case Rock Hill Printing and Finishing, 1977-1990 (Box 107, Folder 50)
- Case - J. Schoeneman (sub. Calvin Clothing) Chambersburg, Pennsylvania, 1990 (Box 107, Folder 51)
- Case - J. Schoeneman (sub. Calvin Clothing) Palm Beach Div. New Bedford, Massachusetts, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 52)
- Case - J. Schoeneman (sub. Calvin Clothing) Owings Mills, Maryland, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 53)
- Case - J. Schoeneman (sub. Calvin Clothing) Wilmington, Delaware, 1993 (Box 107, Folder 54)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens (General) Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1981-1983 (Box 107, Folder 55)
- OSH Case J. P. Stevens and Company Roanoke Rapids, North Carolina, 1974-1979 (Box 107, Folder 56)